churchthemes.com 2016-05-27

# Privacy Policy - churchthemes.com

DreamDolphin Media, LLC, d/b/a churchthemes.com (“churchthemes.com”), has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to the privacy of churchthemes.com users. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

## Information Automatically Logged

Information including, but not limited to, a user’s IP address, browser information, operating system, pages visited and referring pages are logged for internal statistical use, to help diagnose problems, provide user support, prevent and address abuse and to improve the overall quality of our website.

## Information Volunteered

Users must be at least 18 years old to use churchthemes.com or to submit personal information to churchthemes.com.

We collect information volunteered by users including, but not limited to, the account information they provide as a user, newsletter subscription information and information involved in purchasing products or services from churchthemes.com. When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. We collect the e-mail addresses of users who communicate with us via e-mail.

When a user pays on churchthemes.com, credit card details are encrypted and transferred to our payment processor for secure processing. Transaction information including, but not limited to, name and address are collected for the purpose of maintaining an order history. Sensitive financial details including credit/debit card and bank account numbers are never stored by churchthemes.com Personal information including account details are kept private unless explicitly specified by the user.

We will not sell or distribute personal information, including e-mail addresses, to another party unless required by law. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request including, but not limited to, your receipt, download information and critical updates. You will only receive our regular newsletter if you specifically choose to subscribe to it. A user can unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time by contacting churchthemes.com or clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter e-mail.

The information we collect is used to maintain user accounts, personalize user experience, provide support, contact users and improve the quality of our website, customer service, products and services. Non-personally identifying user information may be used by churchthemes.com for research, marketing and informational purposes.

## Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our website. There are appropriate security measures in place in the physical facilities which host and manage this site in order to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from users of churchthemes.com.

Supplied sensitive information, including credit card information, is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a payment, your credit card information will not be stored in our system.

## Cookies

Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer through your web browser (if you allow) that enables sites or service providers to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to record session information that keeps users signed in and to record user-specific information including, but not limited to, pages users access. We use cookies to track referring websites and advertising campaign leads/conversions.

## External Links

churchthemes.com contains links to other sites. churchthemes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Users should access all external sites at their own risk.

## Data Access/Quality

Upon request, we provide users of this website with access to all information that we maintain about them, transaction information, communications that the user has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, inquiries) and contact information (e.g., e-mail address, name, etc.) that we maintain about them. Persons can access this information by contacting us via our contact form at <https://churchthemes.com/contact/>. Upon request, we offer everyone the ability to have inaccuracies in their information corrected or removed.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by signing into their account and editing details.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

## CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://churchthemes.com/terms/>.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. It the user’s responsibility to be aware of the current privacy policy of this website.

Last Update: July 30, 2013

If you have any questions about this privacy policy statement, the practices of this website, your dealings with this website, or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us using the information below.

E-mail (Contact Form): <https://churchthemes.com/contact/>

churchthemes.com  
P.O. Box 126511  
Benbrook, TX 76126  
United States
